(Raj:)I don't know. I lost track
and I missed my exit.
(Raj:)So, uh... so what's up?
(Claire:)Well, last time we talked,
(Claire:)I had just gotten back together
with my boyfriend,
(Claire:)and I wanted to let you know
that things didn't work out.
(Raj:)Really? I'm sorry.
(Raj:)I swear I know other words.
(Claire:)So if you were
still interested...
Yes! Indeed!
Absolutely! Indubitably!
(Raj:)I'm not even sure
what the last one means,
(Raj:)but it's another word,
and I know it.
(Raj:)So, uh,
(Raj:)when do you want to meet up?
(Claire:)Uh, I'm almost off work.
(Claire:)What are you doing now?
R-Right now, well...
(Raj:)Well, actually,
to-to be completely honest,
(Raj:)I'm stopping by
to see my ex-girlfriend
(Raj:)because she's having
a tough time. But...
(Raj:)it's not like we're getting
back together or anything.
(Claire:)Let me guess, the worst part
about breaking up
(Claire:)is that she doesn't have her
best friend to talk to anymore?
That's exactly what she said!
(Raj:)How do you know that?
(Claire:)I'm a girl. It's, like,
page one out of the playbook.
(Raj:)Any chance you could send me
a PDF of that playbook?
(Leonard:)They've been out
there a while.
(Amy:)I hope
everything's okay.